如果我告诉你世界即将毁灭
What if I told you that the world was gonna end
你只有15分钟陪伴我或者朋友
And you had fifteen minutes to spend with me or your friends
你是否愿坐头班车来我家
Would you take the first bus over to my house
或者去坐末班机到西海岸?
Or would you take the last plane over the West Coast
像这样的时刻,变卦的内心
See at times like these with a change of heart
一切已完结,来不及开始
It was over and done before we had a start
这挥之不去,我无所适从
It goes on in my head and I'll wind up dead
唱着,Sha-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
Singing sha-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
如果天上繁星坠向这大地
What if all the stars came crashing to the ground
而爆炸与火光在周围肆意蔓延
And explosions and fires started happening all around
你愿相信我并回家还是隔岸观火?
Would you believe me and come home or sit back, let it be?
我不能自己一人
I can't do this by myself
如果我告诉你世界即将毁灭
What if I told you that the world was gonna end
你只有15分钟陪伴我或者朋友
And you had fifteen minutes to spend with me or your friends
我想我们都用不上手机
I guess we don't even need to use the phone
我不需你回应独自就很好
I don't need your answer, I'll be spending it alone